dog.com 2016-03-15

# Privacy Policy - Dog.com

|  Dog.com >

Privacy Policy

Dog.com respects your privacy and we are committed to protecting it. Dog.com believes in keeping your information confidential. We only collect information from you when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. Any information we collect is used for the purpose of providing you with a more satisfying and personalized shopping and browsing experience.

Dog.com does not share, sell or rent any personal information to other companies or third parties unless you authorize us to do so.  Occasionally we may send you special offers from other TABcom properties. You may opt out of these offers at any time by clicking the opt-out link in the email.

Dog.com collects and uses information in the following ways:

  * **Order Fulfillment** \- When you order from our site, we request your, name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, credit card number and expiration date. This information allows us to process, fulfill and alert you to the status of your order. Dog.com may use this information about your purchases to enhance your shopping experience by notifying you of special promotions, functionality changes and new services that we think you will find valuable. You may choose to remove yourself from this list at any time. To be removed from this list, please contact us online and title your e-mail "No Promotions." We may also monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop the design and layout that best suits our customers.
  * **Surveys, Site Features** \- We may ask you for additional information about you and your behavior and/or about your pet or business. We may request this information, but do not require that you complete this information. This information is requested to help us provide the best possible site and personalized experience on Dog.com. This information will be kept confidential and will be used to help us make Dog.com better for you.
  * **Preferred Customer Offers** \- When you sign-up for the Dog.com Preferred Customer Offers we will ask you for your name and email address. This information is required. We may also ask you some questions in regard to your pet. Our Preferred Customer Offers will contain content and product highlights, and special promotions. As part of these offers and associated promotions, Dog.com may send you information about services and products from partners and other companies that we think may be of interest to you. Please note, that these e-mails are sent by Dog.com and we do NOT give these companies or partners any personally identifiable information about our customers or users. You may choose to remove yourself from our regular email Preferred Customer Offers and/or our partner emails. To be removed, please contact us online. The title of your email should be "No Newsletter", "No Dog.com Promotions", "No Partner Promotions", or combination thereof that you desire.
  * **Catalog** \- When you sign-up to receive the Dog.com Catalog, a monthly publication, Dog.com will ask for your name, address and email address. Your name and address are required to send you the Dog.com Catalog. The email address is optional and may be used to send you special promotions and other items we think may be of interest to you. You may remove your name from our catalog list at any time. To remove your name from our Catalog List, please contact us online and title the email "No Catalog".
  * **Technical Information** \- Dog.com does place a feature on your web browser called a "cookie" to assign each member a unique number. This unique number allows Dog.com to track the items in their Shopping Cart and to save past purchase information. This enhances your experience by saving your Shopping Cart information so that you have the ability to view old orders. Cookies do not allow Dog.com to track the items to collect additional information other than the information that is provided by the member at the time of registration. In addition to cookies, Dog.com may collect technical information which does not allow us to identify you personally but pertains to your use of the Internet. For example, we may collect the type of Internet Browser you are using or type of e-mail messaging capabilities that you have. This information enables us to enhance the content from Dog.com.
  * **Cookies** \- Cookies are small pieces of information stored by your web browser on the computer's hard drive. A cookie may contain information, such as a session identifier, which is used to track the pages of the sites you have visited. Most web browsers are set up to accept cookies; however, you can change your browser settings to refuse cookies. In order to fully enjoy the shopping experience at Dog.com, we recommend you keep your cookies "turned on". 

We currently contract with several online partners to help manage and optimize our Internet business and communications. We use the services of a marketing company to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our site. To do this, we use Web beacons and cookies provided by our marketing company on this site. The type of information we collect includes product codes and prices for merchandise as well as which pages users have visited. By supplementing our records, this information helps us learn things like what pages are most attractive to our visitors, which of our products most interest our customers and what kinds of offers our customers like to see. Although our marketing company logs the information coming from our site on our behalf, we control how the data may and may not be used. If you do not want to help us learn how to improve our site, products, offers and marketing strategy, you can "opt-out" of this website analysis tool by clicking [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Dog.com may share non personal, non-individual aggregate information or summary statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third-party vendors. This information will never include any personally identifiable information. Dog.com is very protective of the privacy of its customers. If at any time Dog.com is required by law or by a legal process to release customer information, we must cooperate fully. 

If you have any questions or concerns about our policies or to have your name and information removed from any of TabCom, LLC's lists or databases, please contact us anytime at:

**Phone:** 1.888.809.0750 

**Email:** Contact us online

**Mail:**  
TabCom, LLC  
Privacy Policy Administration  
1 Maplewood Drive  
Hazleton, PA 18202-9798 

| 

---|---|---
